<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="106">
  <author>LimnedMoonlight</author>
  <version>1.1.0.0</version>

  <title>
    <de>Vertikale Kleinwindkraftanlage Lizard H15</de>
    <en>Vertical Windturbine Lizard H15</en>
    <fr>Turbine Eolienne Verticale Lizard H15</fr>
    <pl>Pionowa Mała Turbina Wiatrowa Lizard H15</pl>
  </title>

  <description>
    <de><![CDATA[
Konzipiert wurde diese Kleinanlage u.a für die autarke Stromversorgung von ländlichen Gegenden, unabhängigen Gebäuden und Häusern.
Vertikal-Anlagen bieten eine vergleichbar hohe Energiedichte auf kleinsten Raum.
Vertikal-Anlagen verursachen weniger Lärm sowie Schattenwirkung und sind Energieeffizienter als die gängigen Horizontal-Anlagen.

Preis: 45250 €
Tägliche Unterhaltskosten: 7 €
Nennleistung: 15 KW
Einkommen pro Monat: 0 - 4.800 €

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Kleine XML-Anpassungen,
- Fehlende BRAND korrigiert,
- Rotationsachse des Windmessers korrigiert (Rotiert nun korrekt),
- Polnische Übersetzung hinzugefügt.]]>
  </de>

  <en><![CDATA[
This small vertical Turbine System was designed for self-sufficient power supply of rural areas, independent buildings and houses.
Vertical systems offer a comparably high energy density in the smallest of spaces.
In addition, they cause less noise and shadow effects and are more energy efficient than the common horizontal systems.

Price: 45250 $
Daily Upkeep: 7 $
Nominal Power: 15 KW
Income per Month: 0 - 4.800 €

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Missing BRAND corrected,
- Minor XML adjustments,
- Corrected the wind gauge's axis of rotation (now rotates correctly).
- Added Polish translation.]]>
  </en>

  <fr><![CDATA[
Ce petit système de turbine verticale a été conçu pour l'alimentation électrique autonome des zones rurales, des bâtiments indépendants et des maisons.
Les systèmes verticaux offrent une densité énergétique relativement élevée dans les espaces les plus réduits.
De plus, ils génèrent moins de bruit et d'effets d'ombre et sont plus efficaces sur le plan énergétique que les systèmes horizontaux courants.

Prix : 45250 $
Entretien quotidien : 7 $
Puissance nominale : 15 KW
Revenu mensuel : 0 - 4 800 €

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Marque manquante corrigée,
- Petites modifications XML,
- Correction de l'axe de rotation de l'anémomètre (il tourne désormais correctement),
- Ajout de la traduction en polonais.]]>
  </fr>

<pl><![CDATA[
Ta niewielka instalacja została zaprojektowana m.in. do samowystarczalnego zasilania obszarów wiejskich, niezależnych budynków i domów.
Instalacje pionowe oferują stosunkowo wysoką gęstość energii na najmniejszej przestrzeni.
Instalacje pionowe powodują mniej hałasu i cienia oraz są bardziej energooszczędne niż popularne instalacje poziome.

Cena: 45250 €
Codzienne koszty utrzymania: 7 €
Moc znamionowa: 15 KW
Dochód miesięczny: 0 - 4800 €

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Brakująca MARKA poprawiona,
- Niewielkie poprawki XML,
- Poprawiono oś obrotu anemometru (teraz obraca się prawidłowo),
- Dodano polskie tłumaczenie.]]>
  </pl>
  </description>

  <iconFilename>icon_h15_vertical.dds</iconFilename>
  <multiplayer supported="true"/>

  <storeItems>
    <storeItem xmlFilename="h15_vertical.xml"/>
  </storeItems>

  <l10n>
    <text name="description">
    <de>Konzipiert wurde diese Kleinanlage u.a für die autarke Stromversorgung von ländlichen Gegenden, unabhängigen Gebäuden und Häusern. Vertikal-Anlagen bieten eine vergl. hohe Energiedichte auf kleinsten Raum.</de>
    <en>This small vertical Turbine System was designed for self-sufficient power supply of rural areas, independent buildings and houses. Vertical systems offer a comparably high energy density in the smallest of spaces.</en>
    <fr>Ce petit système de turbine verticale a été conçu pour l'alimentation électrique autonome des zones rurales, des bâtiments indépendants et des maisons. Les systèmes verticaux offrent une densité énergétique comparativement élevée dans les espaces les plus réduits.</fr>
    <pl>Ta niewielka instalacja została zaprojektowana m.in. do samowystarczalnego zasilania energią elektryczną obszarów wiejskich, niezależnych budynków i domów. Instalacje pionowe oferują stosunkowo wysoką gęstość energii na najmniejszej przestrzeni.</pl>
    </text>

    <text name="name">
    <de>Lizard H15</de>
    <en>Lizard H15</en>
    <fr>Lizard H15</fr>
    <pl>Lizard H15</pl>
    </text>
  </l10n>

</modDesc>
